(Sheldon:)...he is with Wolowitz and Koothrappali
setting up her stereo.
(Penny:)Oh, they're all up there, huh?
Hmm. Typical.
(Sheldon:)It's axiomatically atypical.
(Sheldon:)Until recently, they did not know Alicia, and
had no encounters in a previous location.
(Sheldon:)They never went
to visit the former tenants.
So your characterization of their behavior
as typical is demonstrably fallacious.
(Penny:)Okay, now I see the giant squid head.
[DOOR OPENS THEN CLOSES]
(Sheldon:)Oh, great.
Now I have to start all over again.
(Howard:)Yeah, I thought about renting
this apartment...
...but I'm really more of a downtown-loft
kind of guy.
(Alicia:)Cool. So are you in a loft now?
Oh, actually I'm living
with a woman in Altadena.
Purely platonic. She's also my maid. Heh.
- Sounds like a sweet deal.
- Well, I won't lie. It's pretty dope.